<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Name>ToxicTitan</Name>
  <Author>MerGatto</Author>
  <Version>0.1.0</Version>
  <Description>
    [h1]ToxicTitan[/h1]
    [b]WARNING:[/b] This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.
    See: https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods

    My attempt on titan, inspired by vivi and murk, I created this based on the desire to have a more challenging alternative to Europa.
    This version features 2 different weather events, most often you'll encounter Acid Methane Rain (Volatiles), but occusionally you'll also encounter Snow storms.
    These worldsettings will work on their own but for the intended experience you'll need to have StationeersMods installed (https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods).

    Having StationeersMods enables the following changes:
    - First weather event will occur after 1 day instead of 7
    - First weather event is guaranteed to be Acid Rain
    - Acid Rain and SnowStorms will NOT trigger forced follow up events ('Regular' rain)

    For added challenge I can highly recommend to use Free Lunch's Structure Thermodynamics mod alongside this world (https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3336803492)

    Some tips when playing on this world:
    - Weather events will start very quickly after starting, so your first priority should be to create a safe space to put your stuff
    - Using Airlocks might be dangerous during rain events, since it leaves behind liquid volatiles puddles, which will NOT count towards room pressure. I recommend either using a custom airlock script or a manual airlock with a liquid drain.
    - Solar panels might as well not exist but wind power is quite reliable due to the increased amount of weather events
    - Coal is rather rare on the surface but more abundant when using deep miners
    - Oxide ice is also rather rare, but you can substitute Nitrice instead for furnace usage
    - Use the cold atmosphere to your advantage, Gas fuel generators are rather easy to setup here for example


    Credits:
    vivi - https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198187662981/
    murk - https://steamcommunity.com/id/iammurk
    jixxed - for creating the StationeersMods framework https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods
    pardeike - for creating Harmony https://github.com/pardeike
  </Description>
    <InGameDescription>
    <![CDATA[<size="30"><color=#ffa500> ToxicTitan </color></size>
<b>WARNING:</b> <color=#ff0000>This is a StationeersMods Plugin Mod. It requires Bepinex to be installed with the StationeersMods plugin.</color>
See: https://github.com/jixxed/StationeersMods

Titan, Saturn's largest moon, is a frozen, methane-rich world with treacherous storms and toxic rain, offering both danger and potential for human survival.
]]>
  </InGameDescription>
    <ChangeLog>
    [h3]Version 0.1.0:[/h3]
    [list]
    [*]Initial release
    [/list]
  </ChangeLog>
  <Tags>
    <Tag>World Settings</Tag>
    <Tag>Start Conditions</Tag>
    <Tag>StationeersMods</Tag>
  </Tags>
  <LoadBefore>
    <ModId>1</ModId>
  </LoadBefore>
</ModMetadata>